gossimer.com 2004-06-07

# Gossimer - Affordable Web Hosting

**Please read the below statement for information regarding Gossimer's privacy policy about what information we collect, and what we do with that information.**

  * Please read our [FAQ's](http://www.gossimer.com/cgi-bin/faq/index.cgi) section for answers to our most frequently asked questions.

  * By signing up for any of our services you have agreed that you have read and understood our privacy policy and are bound by this site's  [terms and conditions](http://www.gossimer.com/terms.html).

##  Privacy Statement for Gossimer Network

gossimer has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [http://www.gossimer.com](http://www.gossimer.com/)

####  Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to administer our public services on our Web site.  Gossimer Network does not approve of SPAM, harassment of anyone in our chat rooms, forums, or any of our other public services, so as a protection we may record your IP address to help ensure everyone's safety and enjoyment of all of our services.

####  Cookies

Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly.  In order to differ the advertisements that you see on our web pages we may use cookies to ensure that you don't see the same ad repeatedly. 

We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.  Some of our services hosted on this website may use cookies to record your demographics so that we may provide content that is pertinent to your local area.

####  Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

####  Registration Forms

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address), financial information (like their bank account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).

Contact information from the registration forms is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers, and to get in touch with the customer when necessary.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.  
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.  

We do NOT share any personal information with anyone, not even our advertisers.  Personal information is information such as your name, mailing address, email address, income, etc.  

####  Order Forms

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).

Contact information from the order forms is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications for registration, and to bill the user for products and services.

Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.  
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

We do NOT share any personal information with anyone, not even our advertisers.  Personal information is information such as your name, mailing address, email address, income, etc.

####  Surveys

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like email address), and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level).

Contact information from the surveys is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.  
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

We do NOT share any personal information with anyone, not even our advertisers.  Personal information is information such as your name, mailing address, email address, income, etc.

####  Contests

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like email address), unique identifiers (like social security number), and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level).

Contact information from the contests is used to send promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.  
This information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

We do NOT share any personal information with anyone, not even our advertisers.  Personal information is information such as your name, mailing address, email address, income, etc.

####  External Links

This site contains links to other sites. gossimer is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

####  Special Relationships

Some of the services provided on this website are hosted or powered by other companies.  gossimer does not have control over any of their privacy practices, nor do we have the ability to receive any information they obtain from you.  

####  Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.  Gossimer Network will not be held responsible for any information you supply to anyone in the public areas of our website.

NOTE: No one affiliated with Gossimer Network will never ask you for personal information in any of our public areas, we will only ask for personal information privately by email, phone, or mail.

####  Children's Guidelines

We at gossimer care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children:

  1. We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent.

  2. We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent

  3. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to:

    1. Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes.

    2. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification.

    3. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity.

  4. We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service.

  5. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child from Gossimer Network upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child.

  6. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected.

  7. We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children.

  8. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online.

####  Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us .

  1. You can send email to [ remove@gossimer.net](mailto:remove@gossimer.net)[ ](mailto:remove@gossimer.net)to be removed from anything mailing list sent to you by the Gossimer Network.

##  Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
